[microphone feedback]
[♪ opening theme music playing]
FLEX X COP 2
CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
[♪ suspenseful, ominous music playing]
[♪ ominous sting plays, fades]
RESIDENT REGISTRATION CARD
JIN ISOO
[Seongwon] After all,
you're my Little Prince.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ tense, pulsating music playing]
[exhales softly]
Where is Isoo right now?
[♪ music increases in tempo]
FINAL EPISODE
Did he go to my exhibition hall?
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music slows]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
- [grunts, exclaims]
- [grunts]
- [Isoo grunts]
- [heavy thud]
[panting]
[groans]
- [blunt thud]
- [high-pitched ringing]
[thuds]
[high-pitched ringing fades]
[distorted thud]
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
[line ringing]
- [fire roaring]
- [cell phone vibrating]
[tires screech]
How did it go?
- There's a fire inside.
- What?
Isoo! Jin Isoo!
Jin Isoo!
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[grunts]
[all exclaim]
Jin Isoo!
Isoo!
Isoo! Jin Isoo!
Jin Isoo!
Get him on my back! [grunts]
Jin Isoo! Get on my back!
[Changun grunting]
Call an ambulance!
[♪ music resumes tempo]
[Changun grunts]
[panting] Jin Isoo.
Can you hear me?
[sirens approaching]
The ambulance is on its way.
Hang in there.
[sirens blaring]
[tires screech]
[Changun] Here. He's here.
Over here!
[♪ suspenseful, ominous music playing]
Detective Jin found all the evidence.
Evidence?
What evidence?
The victims' belongings and photos.
You have them all on display.
Ah.
Really?
I wonder what he thought of it.
[cell phone vibrating]
[♪ music fades]
CHIEF PARK CHANGUN
- You should get that.
- [cell phone continues vibrating]
It seems urgent.
[panting] Detective Joo!
[♪ tense, ominous music playing]
[door slams]
[breathes deeply]
There's a basement inside my studio.
Tell your boyfriend to burn it down.
I might have a visitor.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music swells, fades]
[Hyera panting] Chief.
What about Isoo?
Ah, well...
[♪ somber, suspenseful music playing]
He's in surgery right now.
He has a brain hemorrhage.
[sighs heavily]
[Hyera sighs softly]
What do we do?
Don't worry too much.
They said they can stop the bleeding.
Detective Jin is going to be okay.
What exactly happened?
When we got there, Isoo was unconscious,
and the basement was on fire.
- [exhales softly]
- You mean someone set the place on fire?
Yes.
That person must have attacked Isoo.
We're searching through
all the nearby security footage...
but the basement was destroyed.
We won't find any evidence.
[sighs softly]
- [cell phone vibrating]
- [sighs heavily]
Yes, how did it go?
Then widen the search area.
[angrily] Get a list of all the vehicles
spotted near the studio!
[Kyungjin sighs softly]
Yu Seongwon, that son of a bitch.
[voice shaking] I should've gone with him.
[sighs regretfully]
- [Hyera sighs]
- [sighs heavily]
The police chief said you are free to go.
SURGERY STATUS
JIN ISOO, 32Y/O MALE, IN SURGERY
[♪ music fades]
Bro!
[♪ gentle, melancholy music playing]
How did it go?
The surgery went well.
But on top of the trauma to his brain,
he suffered carbon monoxide poisoning,
so it's difficult to say
when he will regain consciousness.
Right, we'll move him to his room.
We'll look into the suspect's vehicle.
Mmm.
Jin Isoo.
You'll wake up, right?
I know you won't let this break you.
I'll be waiting.
Sleep for a bit, then come back.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
[cell phone vibrating]
Jin Isoo is still alive.
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
[line disconnects]
[monitor beeping steadily]
[♪ somber, melancholy music playing]
Chairman Choi.
[breath trembles]
Detective Joo Hyera.
I'm sorry.
Please leave.
I will stay here.
[door closes]
[♪ music fades]
NUMBER 1 SAFETY!! NUMBER 1 PUBLIC ORDER!!
GANGHA POLICE STATION
[sighs softly]
[scoffs softly]
[♪ suspenseful, ominous music playing]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[exhales softly]
Should I just disappear?
[scoffs softly]
Should I make one final piece?
[♪ music fades]
[monitor beeping steadily]
[♪ gentle, melancholy music playing]
[grunts softly]
Is he awake?
[sighs heavily]
No.
Go on in.
I'll go talk to his doctor.
GANGHA JUNGANG HOSPITAL
VIP WING
[monitor beeping steadily]
[cell phone vibrating]
Hello?
[Kyungjin] Is Isoo awake?
He's still the same.
Did you find anything?
We found a vehicle
that could be the suspect's,
but the plate is fake.
We'll keep looking.
[♪ music fades]
[Kyungjin sighs softly]
[Junyoung exhales softly]
[pats back]
Get it together.
We need to catch that bastard.
[sighs deeply] Okay.
[sighs heavily]
I don't know about Yu Seongwon,
but if Jeong Taeseon ordered
someone to do it,
it's probably him.
[♪ somber, suspenseful music playing]
But he went off the grid
after killing Cho Pilgu.
We don't even know his name.
[sighs thoughtfully]
Is there any way to track the car
after it left the studio?
I checked all the traffic cameras,
but it disappeared.
Did the suspect ditch the car somewhere?
Let's search the area again
from where it disappeared.
Mmm, the car disappeared around here.
- Let's go.
- [cell phone vibrating]
INCOMING CALL
NO CALLER ID
Yes, this is Park Junyoung.
[unknown caller] Ah.
We are Detective Jin Isoo's... [mouthing]
His secret agents.
What?
We saw on the news
that Detective Jin was in an accident.
So?
He asked us to find someone for him.
[whispering] A guy who killed a suspect.
Did you find him?
[secret agent] We found him.
How?
Ah.
[♪ upbeat rock music playing]
That will remain a secret.
His name is Han Jonghyeon.
Date of birth is November 19, 1983.
IDENTITY SEARCH
NAME HAN JONGHYEON
[secret agent] His recent location
is Wonmok-dong.
It seems he's at a hotel
called East Hill Hotel.
Thank you.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
[♪ music fades]
[cell phone vibrating]
Hello?
[Taeseon] No matter how I look at it...
[♪ tense, ominous music playing]
...to cover all this up,
I think Seongwon
will have to commit suicide.
A mentally unstable artist
takes his life
after his studio burns down.
The murder cases are closed unsolved.
[♪ ominous chord swells, fades]
And I'll become a poor mother
who lost her child.
Yes, understood.
Do you still have what I gave you?
He's not easy to deal with.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
There's no telling what he'll do.
Be careful.
When it's done,
leave the country.
I'll come find you.
I'm always grateful to you.
You know you're the only one
I can trust, right?
Yes. Please don't worry.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
It's this place.
EAST HILL HOTEL
[♪ suspenseful, foreboding music playing]
That's Han Jonghyeon.
You're right.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
- [cell phone vibrating]
- [exhales sharply]
JEONG TAESEON
[sighs softly]
[Taeseon] I sent you a car.
Come to the villa.
[♪ tense, ominous music playing]
Should we get him now?
No.
Let's wait and see.
[exhales softly]
[♪ pulsating foreboding music playing]
- [sighs softly]
- Please get in.
The chairwoman sent me to escort you.
[inhales sharply]
[cell phone vibrating]
Detective Joo, we found the suspect
who killed Cho Pilgu.
Han Jonghyeon used to be
Jeong Taeseon's chief secretary.
He's on the move with Yu Seongwon.
We're following them.
Where are you? I'll be right there.
Near Haseong. We'll keep you updated.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
[Seongwon sighs softly]
[♪ suspenseful, foreboding music playing]
Where are we going?
This isn't the way to the villa.
[sighs deeply]
Did my mom tell you to kill me?
Did she tell you
to lock me up in a psych ward again?
[breathes deeply]
That's what you get for pushing your luck.
[♪ pulsating foreboding music playing]
[Seongwon exhales heavily]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[scoffing softly]
[♪ music turns ominous]
- [distant gunshot]
- What was that?
[engine revving]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ suspenseful, foreboding music playing]
[tires screech]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
- [tires screeching]
- [engine revving]
[tires screeching]
[engine accelerating]
- [explosive crash]
- [glass shattering]
- [violent crunching]
- [debris rattling]
[chuckles]
- [engine whirring in reverse]
- [tires screeching]
- [engine revving]
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
[motorcycle approaching]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[engine idles, shuts off]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[leaves rustling]
[grunts]
Detective Park.
Detective Choi!
Detective Park, wake up.
[breathing frantically]
[♪ music fades]
EMERGENCY WARD
[monitors beeping steadily]
[hisses in pain]
- [sighs softly]
- [cell phone vibrating]
Hello?
[Byungsik] Yu Seongwon ditched the car
and disappeared.
[♪ somber, suspenseful music playing]
There aren't any cameras here.
We'll widen the search area.
[sighs wearily]
[panting] Junyoung.
Jiwon.
How did this happen?
You're badly hurt.
No, I just hurt my neck a little.
[shuddering exhale]
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
I'm just glad you're okay.
[inhales softly]
[Hyera sighs softly]
[Hyera] We're out of options. [sighs]
I'll finish this.
Please look after Isoo.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music fades]
JONGHYEON
[line ringing]
[automated voice] The number
you have dialed is unavailable...
You can't go in there.
[♪ somber, suspenseful music playing]
Han Jonghyeon was murdered.
[door closes]
Did you order him to kill Yu Seongwon?
What do you mean?
This looks like an accident.
My team was following Han Jonghyeon.
Yu Seongwon killed him and disappeared.
So what?
Yu Seongwon will now
come to kill you.
[scoffs]
- Hmm.
- All the evidence is gone,
and he may have considered
leaving like this,
but now that his own mother
tried to kill him,
he won't hold back.
He's been obsessed with dead bodies
and murder since he was a child.
You knew, didn't you?
But all you did was
try to hide it and cover it up.
You'll pay the price for that.
If you cooperate with us
and confess to everything that's happened,
we'll protect you.
You will
protect me?
Yes.
If it means we can catch Yu Seongwon.
[scoffs] I don't need it.
I know my son best.
That boy...
can't go against me.
Without me, his life is over, too.
If we don't catch Yu Seongwon now,
you'll have to spend
the rest of your life living in fear.
Never knowing when your son...
might sneak in and kill you.
Are you okay with that?
Then the next time I see you,
I'll be looking at your dead body.
[footsteps receding]
[♪ suspenseful, foreboding music playing]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ suspenseful, ominous music playing]
Mom.
What are you doing here?
You don't come to my exhibitions.
What?
Are you worried there's evidence here?
[sighs]
Now you're trying
to get rid of my work, too?
[Seongwon] Huh?
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
Joo Hyera?
[sighs softly]
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
You posed as the victims
to create an alibi, didn't you?
I tried it myself.
How does it feel
to be on the receiving end?
[sighs softly]
Then the next time I see you,
I'll be looking at your dead body.
[footsteps receding]
[Taeseon] Wait.
[♪ suspenseful, pulsating music playing]
How will you catch him?
I'll pretend to be you.
What?
Are you disappointed I'm not your mom?
No, it's fine.
[exhales softly] I've always wanted
to use you as a model, too.
The detective who was after me
failed to catch me
and became my art in the end.
[chuckles]
Joo Hyera.
How do you want to die?
[♪ music turns ominous]
[scoffs]
How do you want to die?
Today's that day.
I was obsessed with you.
I wanted to stop you.
And I wanted to catch you.
But now I'm out of options.
I'll have to kill you.
[scoffs]
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
[grunts, groans]
[groans]
[Seongwon grunting]
- [exhales sharply]
- [grunts]
[groaning]
[dull thud]
Do you get it now?
[groaning]
This is the death you love so much.
[laughing maniacally]
[breathing heavily]
You... [exhales heavily]
...will become a masterpiece.
- [gunshot]
- [squelch]
[distorted thud]
[♪ tense, ominous music playing]
[sighs in relief]
[chuckles]
[grunts softly]
[♪ pulsating foreboding music playing]
[exhales sharply]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[Isoo] Yu Seongwon!
[♪ music resumes tempo]
Isoo!
[♪ suspenseful, ominous music playing]
I'm glad you're here.
You need to witness this piece.
You crazy bastard.
It's not finished yet.
Just watch how I turn this woman
into a work of art.
It's the final piece you'll see
before you die.
A work of art?
[♪ music swells]
[shattering]
[♪ gripping, ominous music playing]
Is this a work of art?
[shattering, scattering]
[panting]
This is a work of art?
This is just garbage.
Garbage created by a psychotic killer.
You think you're an artist?
You just want to kill people.
Because you have
this sick obsession with dead bodies.
You dress it up as art
and proudly show it off
for people to see...
but you're just insane.
[sighs heavily]
Do you still not get it?
This is art on a whole other level!
The people I killed
were living meaningless lives.
But I turned them
into something eternally beautiful!
Jo Nayeong.
She couldn't get hired
as a flight attendant,
so she went from
one part-time job to another.
She lived a miserable life
in a basement studio,
but I turned her into something beautiful!
- [Nayeong whimpering softly]
- [Seongwon grunting]
- [whimpering]
- [grunting]
ECSTASY
A BREATHLESS FALL
No one so much as gave her a second look
when she was alive.
But now everyone looks at her
and calls her a beautiful work of art.
Choi Yeongmin.
He had a great body.
So I used a knife.
[♪ melancholy piano music playing]
- [squelch]
- [blood splatters]
[♪ ominous sting plays]
[chuckles softly]
[Seongwon] The blood in the air
looked like stars.
CLIMAX
LIGHT SCATTERED ACROSS THE UNIVERSE
And Jeong Minjae.
He blossomed like a flower.
[wet dripping]
[laughs maliciously]
Do you know why people love my work?
They can feel that death is present here
without needing to be told.
Everyone has that urge.
"I want to know death."
"I want to see death."
In the past, they held public executions.
The people watching
would've felt a sense of catharsis.
The exhilaration of being alive
in the face of death.
The desire for true life!
[yelling] That!
That is what I showed them!
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
I think this is enough.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[Hyera] Thanks for the confession.
[♪ dramatic sting plays]
[♪ music fades]
FOUR HOURS EARLIER
We're out of options. [sighs]
- I'll finish this.
- [monitor beeping steadily]
[♪ somber, suspenseful music playing]
Please look after Isoo.
Mmm.
[Isoo, muffled]
What are you planning to do?
[Mr. Choi] Isoo!
- [Hyera] Are you okay?
- [groans softly]
[exhales heavily]
I slept like a log
and now I'm completely refreshed.
[sighs in relief]
So?
How are you going to finish this?
Ah... [sighs]
I'll have to pressure
Jeong Taeseon into confessing.
That won't work on her.
Let's set something up.
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
He has a gun?
Yes.
Han Jonghyeon had a gun,
and Yu Seongwon took it.
[panting softly]
Then he'll get even more reckless.
Actually,
that could work to our advantage.
What?
I'll be the bait and lure Yu Seongwon out.
No.
I'll be the bait.
Just explain what the plan is.
[♪ music swells]
- [exhales heavily]
- [♪ music fades]
[vest straps fastening]
[sighs in exasperation]
[Velcro ripping]
I still think it's too dangerous.
Will you be okay?
[Velcro ripping]
[sighs softly]
- I'll make him shoot here.
- [sighs in exasperation]
[♪ tense, ticking music playing]
[Velcro ripping]
Isoo. You're still not fully recovered.
I'm really excited right now.
I feel great just thinking
about catching Yu Seongwon. Mmm!
Mr. Choi.
I need to ask you a favor.
Please get the press together
so we can broadcast live.
UBS might try something,
so call all the foreign outlets, too.
[♪ upbeat rock music playing]
All right.
I'm off.
[grunts, groans]
[groans]
- [exhales sharply]
- [grunts softly]
[grunts]
You... [breathing heavily]
...will become a masterpiece.
- [gunshot]
- [squelch]
[Isoo] Because you have
this sick obsession with dead bodies.
You dress it up as art
and proudly show it off
for people to see...
but you're just insane.
[sighs heavily] Do you still not get it?
This is art on a whole other level!
The people I killed
were living meaningless lives.
But I turned them
into something eternally beautiful!
Jo Nayeong.
She couldn't get hired
as a flight attendant,
so she went from
one part-time job to another.
She lived a miserable life
in a basement studio,
but I turned her into something beautiful!
Everyone, this is a secret mission,
so please just watch quietly.
- What's the secret mission?
- [reporters murmuring]
[reporter 1] What's going on?
They can feel that death is present here
without needing to be told.
[♪ tense, ominous music playing]
[chuckles]
- [♪ music swells]
- [gunshot]
- [grunts]
- [heavy thud]
[♪ theme music playing]
[panting] Crazy bastard.
Here.
- Yu Seongwon.
- [handcuffs clicking]
For the murders of Jo Nayeong...
- [whimpers]
- [Hyera] ...Choi Yeongmin, Kim Heejun,
and Jeong Minjae, you are under arrest.
[breathing heavily]
[murmuring]
There they come.
[reporter 2] He's here!
[reporter 3] Did you confess
to the serial murders?
[reporter 4] When did you
first start killing people?
[clamoring]
You're a pretty big name,
so I called all the foreign press here.
[clamoring continues]
[♪ music fades]
[newscaster 1] This is breaking news.
Sculptor Yu Seongwon's serial murder
confession was broadcast live tonight.
In a shocking revelation, the victims
were the models for his artwork.
[newscaster 2, in English]
This is ANN News.
Seongwon Yu confessed he derived pleasure
from killing his victims.
Prosecutors say he showed no remorse,
even going so far as to belittle
the lives of those he killed.
[newscaster 3] Meanwhile,
police have opened an investigation
after reports suggested
there may have been similar disappearances
during the time Yu was studying
in the United Kingdom.
[♪ somber, suspenseful music playing]
[door closes]
Why aren't you going in?
Ah.
I handed in my resignation.
Your resignation...
has been rejected.
[♪ upbeat rock music playing]
Now, go.
Take him down.
Yes, Chief.
[♪ music fades]
[Isoo exhales contentedly]
All right, since you've already confessed,
let's have an honest conversation.
Confessed?
Was that a confession?
What I said earlier
was about the things I'd imagined
while working with those models.
It's not real.
Wait, you actually believed that?
Was my acting that convincing?
Forensics is investigating
your studio right now.
Let's see how you hold out
until we find the evidence.
Evidence?
Will you find any?
Someone seems to have burned it down.
[♪ suspenseful, pulsating music playing]
[objects clattering]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[distant clanking]
[camera shutter clicking]
[♪ music swells]
[cell phone vibrates]
Detective Park,
I noticed something strange.
[♪ music fades]
Hey.
By any chance,
are you waiting for you mom?
She's in the next room.
She's here to cooperate
with the investigation
and reveal the entire truth.
[♪ somber, suspenseful music playing]
It's time you stood on your own two feet.
You can't depend on your mom forever.
[Changun] Did you know
the person who hired Cho Pilgu...
[inhales sharply]
...to kill Kim Younghwan was Yu Seongwon?
Are you saying
you gave the order to kill him?
Yes.
Why?
Just because. I thought it'd be fun.
No.
You knew, and that's why you ordered
your secretary, Han Jonghyeon,
to kill Cho Pilgu while he was in custody.
Isn't that right?
I...
didn't know anything.
I'm telling the truth.
Well done.
[Changun] You didn't know anything?
Didn't Detective Joo Hyera
make it clear to you?
Your son is a murderer.
He killed five people.
[Taeseon] You know, don't you?
I thought she had it wrong.
I never imagined
that my son could've done
something like that.
Then why did Han Jonghyeon kill Cho Pilgu?
Maybe Seongwon asked him to do it.
They were close, like brothers.
[♪ music fades]
Chairwoman Jeong is still denying
she knows anything.
She claims Yu Seongwon must have
put Han Jonghyeon up to it.
What about Yu Seongwon?
He keeps insisting it wasn't a confession.
[sighs softly]
What about Han Jonghyeon's phone?
There's a record of him calling
the chairwoman, but no recording.
Ah, so... [inhales sharply]
I do have a recording,
but it's from a bug, so we can't use it.
You planted a bug?
Yes.
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
[Taeseon] To cover all this up,
I think Seongwon
will have to commit suicide.
A mentally unstable artist
takes his life
after his studio burns down.
The murder cases are closed unsolved.
And I'll become a poor mother
who lost her child.
[exhales incredulously]
She told him to kill her own son.
That's why Yu Seongwon killed
Han Jonghyeon.
Detective Park and Detective Choi
witnessed that, so we can prove that.
No.
Han Jonghyeon had a gun,
so he'll just claim self-defense.
If we want to prove his serial murders...
We need something from the studio.
We need to unmask that woman, too.
You should talk to the police chief.
I can't go into detail
because I made a promise,
but I think they know each other.
[♪ music fades]
[door opens]
[Taegyun] What?
What is it?
Chairwoman Jeong Taeseon
mentioned you, sir.
How did this happen?
I only told her we had a suspect.
That's all I told her. About Hwang Jongsu.
- How could you tell her that?
- [nervously] Uh...
I really didn't know!
How could I have known
that Yu Seongwon really was a killer?
Chief Park, what do I do?
What do I do?
What am I going to do?
[♪ suspenseful, ticking music playing]
What happened with the Hwang Jongsu case?
Hwang Jongsu?
How is that a case? He committed suicide.
[bangs table]
Inducing suicide is a crime, too.
I know the police chief
gave you information
about our suspect, Hwang Jongsu.
Did you send reporters there
to put pressure on Detective Jin,
then tell Hwang to commit suicide?
What are you talking about?
He asked me to send our news team
because detectives were chasing him.
He said he wanted to go on camera
and declare his innocence.
Mr. Hwang probably died
because of Jin Isoo.
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
Maybe he pushed him from behind.
Over here.
[police dogs panting]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[sniffing eagerly]
[police dogs panting, sniffing]
[barking]
[both barking]
[♪ music swells, fades]
Your mom seems determined
to pin everything on you.
She says you ordered
the murder of Cho Pilgu.
She says she knows nothing.
Who's Cho Pilgu?
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
Can you prove a single thing
you've been saying?
All the people you claim I killed
were still alive after they met me.
The murder display in my studio?
It burned down.
Cho Pilgu, who killed Kim Younghwan,
Han Jonghyeon, who killed Cho Pilgu,
and even Mr. Hwang,
the suspect you were chasing,
are all dead.
[♪ suspenseful, pulsating music playing]
You failed.
Just admit it.
[cell phone vibrating]
DETECTIVE PARK JUNYOUNG
[♪ music swells]
[Junyoung] We found them.
Three bodies were buried in his yard.
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
We found the bodies in your yard.
You buried the bodies in your yard,
walked over them,
and drank tea,
making them look up to you even in death.
You're right.
Because they're mine.
They're mine.
Mine.
Even their bodies rotting inside the earth
are all mine.
- [bangs table]
- [angrily] They're my art!
[shuddering breath of rage]
So this is your ending.
A murderer who pretended to be an artist.
No.
My name, my art
will become even more famous.
[yelling] The whole world
will remember me forever.
[shuddering breath of rage]
You're right.
[in a low voice] Ah...
- [Isoo] That's true.
- [chuckling]
But you
won't get to see that.
You'll be behind bars.
Actually, instead of prison,
you might end up
in a psychiatric hospital.
[♪ melancholy piano music playing]
What a shame.
You hate being locked up
in a hospital room.
Dr. Seo told me everything.
Looks like you'll be wearing
a straitjacket again.
[chuckles softly]
Have fun.
[Seongwon's breath trembling]
[screaming]
[♪ somber, ominous music playing]
[breathing raggedly]
[gasping sharply]
[whimpering brokenly]
[screaming hysterically]
[♪ music fades]
I think I've cooperated enough.
- Need I do more?
- Let's stop here.
[sighs wearily]
Chairwoman.
Where are you going?
Ms. Jeong Taeseon.
You are under arrest for soliciting
the murder of Cho Pilgu and Yu Seongwon.
What are you doing? Do you have proof?
I played this for your son,
and he hit the roof.
[Taeseon] To cover all this up,
I think Seongwon
will have to commit suicide.
A mentally unstable artist
takes his life
after his studio burns down.
[scoffs sarcastically]
[breathes deeply]
[♪ upbeat, jaunty music playing]
You bugged my office?
Yes.
See? What did I tell you?
You should've come here
wearing the 18-karat bracelet I gave you.
Just look at the mess you're in.
It breaks my heart.
Go inside and talk to our handsome chief.
Go back inside.
- Jin Isoo.
- Hurry back inside.
Jin Isoo. I'll make you pay for this!
I'll make you pay!
Oh, I'm not scared at all.
[chuckles]
[door closes]
SHOCKING ARREST OF MOTHER AND SON
A CONFESSION THAT SHOCKED THE WORLD
[camera shutter clicking]
POLICE CHIEF FACES DISCIPLINARY HEARING
MOTHER SOLICITS MURDER TO PROTECT HER SON
JIN ISOO HOLDS JOINT FUNERAL FOR VICTIMS
MAY THEY REST IN PEACE
HANSU GROUP,
GANGHA POLICE STATION, JOO HYERA
OUR DEEPEST CONDOLENCES
MAY THEY REST IN PEACE
CHOI YEONGMIN, KIM HEEJUN, JO NAYEONG
[♪ somber, melancholy music playing]
Let us have a moment of silence.
[woman sobbing]
[scattered sobbing]
Thank you.
[scattered sobbing, sniffling]
[woman sobbing bitterly]
[scattered sobbing, sniffling continues]
[woman] I can't bear
to let you go like this.
How can I let you go?
[woman continues sobbing bitterly]
Thank you.
[breath trembles, sniffles]
[♪ somber, melancholy music continues]
[♪ music fades]
I suddenly couldn't breathe
and my body just froze.
I couldn't even trust myself.
I even wondered
if I should quit being a cop.
But after I caught Yu Seongwon,
I've been sleeping well,
and I feel more at ease.
I somehow feel like
I can get through this.
I'm glad to hear that.
I think doing meaningful work
is helping you get better.
Exactly.
Thank goodness I became a detective.
Investigating is so much fun,
catching bad guys is so rewarding,
and my teammates... [chuckles softly]
They're clueless, but they're good people.
Would you like to see? Here.
[♪ jaunty music playing]
This tall, feeble-looking one
is Detective Joo.
- Okay.
- The right, tall one.
He has a girlfriend now. He's Junyoung.
The curly hair is our youngest teammate.
He claims he has a girlfriend.
And this good-looking man here.
That's me. This is
Violent Crime Investigation Team 1.
- I see.
- Amazing, right?
Gangha Police Violent Crime Team 1,
in investigating a serial murder case
whose perpetrator had long evaded
capture through sophisticated methods,
apprehended the suspect with outstanding
investigative skill and determination,
and demonstrated exemplary dedication
and devotion to duty as police officers,
and is hereby commended.
Gangha Police Violent Crime Team 1,
Senior Inspector Joo Hyera.
[all applauding]
What's wrong with you?
[announcer] Gangha Police Violent Crime
Team 1, Senior Inspector Jin Isoo.
[all applauding]
[loudly] Thank you, sir!
[laughing]
[announcer] Inspector Park Junyoung.
[squeals] You're so handsome,
Park Junyoung!
[all applauding]
[loudly] Thank you, sir!
[announcer] Senior Police Officer
Choi Kyungjin.
[all applauding]
[loudly] Thank you, sir!
Hurry up and get in here. Ready?
- One, two, three!
- [camera shutter clicks]
Perfect.
Huh?
Mr. Choi, I think
you're late for your flight.
I'm not late.
Ah! You're late. Let's take my car.
- [Mr. Choi] I'm fine.
- Let's go. We're off.
- Sorry, goodbye.
- No problem. Goodbye.
[♪ music fades]
[engine purring smoothly]
Are you really going to go like that?
Why would you wear
a suit on a trip to Europe?
I told you, I'm comfortable in this.
But it's a long-haul flight.
- [sighs in exasperation] I give up.
- [chuckles]
[♪ gentle, tender music playing]
Have fun, get plenty of rest,
and take your full vacation.
All right. Thank you.
Did you pack your meds?
If anything happens--
Ah, all right, now stop.
[sighs] I'm worried.
Maybe I should go with you.
I heard your team is
going on vacation as a reward.
We can change the destination to Europe.
I must decline.
[chuckles softly]
[both chuckle]
[♪ music fades]
Have a great trip.
All right. Take care.
I don't feel good sending you off so far.
How about a hug?
[chuckles]
[♪ gentle, tender music playing]
[chuckles softly]
[Isoo exhales contentedly]
Mmm.
I'll be back soon.
Go on inside.
[chuckles softly]
[sighs contentedly]
Mr. Choi Jeonghun.
Oh! [chortles]
Hello.
Where are you going? A business trip?
No.
I'm going on vacation.
Finally.
- Wow.
- [both chuckle]
I'm leaving today, too.
- Really?
- Where are you headed?
I'm going to...
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Me too.
[chuckles]
[chuckles softly]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ upbeat rock music playing]
[exhales contentedly]
Bro. I thought we were going abroad.
We can't just take off as Korean cops.
We have a country to protect.
Having said that,
this is our reward vacation.
Yeah. [exhales contentedly]
I can't remember the last time
I had a break like this.
[sighs contentedly]
What's taking so long?
Women always take forever.
Oh. What are they even doing in there?
[scoffs]
Are you going for a dive?
Whatever.
- Is this good?
- What's with the whistle?
Aren't we going out there?
Right, we should.
- Let's go!
- Move out!
- [Kyungjin] Let's go!
- [Isoo] Let's go!
REWARD VACATION!!
JIN ISOO'S TREAT!
[♪ upbeat pop music playing]
- Whoo!
- [screaming]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ suspenseful, ominous music playing]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music swells]
[exhales heavily]
[♪ music fades]
[exhales softly]
Jin Isoo, get changed.
Why?
[sighs] We have a case.
A case?
Looks like we've got ourselves...
A most interesting case, right?
Let's go, Detective Joo.
[microphone feedback]
We have a case.
Let's go.
[♪ theme music playing]
FLEX X COP 2
EPISODE 14
VIOLENT CRIME TEAM 1
OFF TO THE NEXT CASE!
Special Cast. Yoo Seungho
Special Cast. Kim Hyeeun
Special Cast. Kim Jihun
JIN ISOO
AHN BOHYUN
JOO HYERA
JUNG EUNCHAE
PARK JUNYOUNG
KANG SANGJUN
CHOI KYUNGJIN
KIM SHINBI
YOON JIWON
JUNG GAHEE
YU SEONGWON
YOO SEUNGHO
PARK CHANGUN, LEE DOYEOP
CHOI JEONGHUN, KIM MYOUNGSU
KIM GYEOL, BAEK INJOO,
LEE EUNSANG, KIM SUWON
GWON TAEGYUN, RYU TAEHO
JEONG MINJAE, LIM JINSEOP
KANG JINGYEONG, JEON SOOAH
KCSI LEADER, LEE TAEGEOM
JEONG TAESEON, KIM HYEEUN
HAN JONGHYEON, MOON JINSEUNG
FLEX X COP 2
THE END
Translated by Hyesoo Lee